I
Have a question for you. Yeah, what is it? Why were you talking to Yozara in that dream? I mean if you went back ten years
Why was what what are you talking about? She's talking about how you were sleep talking you kept shouting Yozara
Yozara, Yozara, don't you think that's kind of weird? Are you serious?
You guys there's nothing at all strange about me showing up in a dream that took place when he was younger
We played together when we were little kids
You played together like you and Kodika did did I stutter it was a long time ago Kodika moved away from here for about ten years
But before that we both went to the same school we hung out and played and all that stuff
So I guess you could say we were friends friends
Well, why have you never said anything look we were friends when we were kids. It's not like it's personal
Honestly, I didn't think anybody would even care about it. I don't get why it's such a big deal
Rika had a feeling something fishy was up. You were friends. Rika didn't expect that though. Yeah, I didn't either
any other suggestions guess it's back to normal
thanks hey that reminds me don't we have a school festival coming up
kodaka i believe you just stepped on a landmine explain that no never mind in fact i don't even
know what those words mean whatever the school festival is all a lie anyway come on you're being
ridiculous and this time no one's sure why think about it we're talking about a school festival
here also known as an event for people with real lives also known as not us hey i see your point
uh-huh i thought you might yeah i suppose an event like that has nothing to do with losers like us
shut your mouth don't lump everyone into loserville with you just so you know i'm a big deal at this
school and i was all over last year's festival they couldn't get enough of me true rika remember
seeing a lot of senna last year she watched the festivities from the guest seating on the president's
personal invitation see so you can tell them how amazing i was now go ahead rika and don't leave
anything out either oh okay well i saw you in a bunch of the athletic competitions that's right
like running the 200 meter dash as well as the scavenger hunt race and of course the obstacle course
i did the bread eating race and i rocked the marathon oh and my favorite was the mock cavalry
battle it was awesome as was myself wow that's impressive senna thanks i did the culture stuff too
i'm more than an athlete right rika saw you in the class play senna bravely cut down all the bad
guys with her sword yeah no surprise there i was the star of the show no matter what it was you were
the one way more into it than anybody else which was awkward everybody there was super annoyed don't
be hateful that's not true all of the audiences went crazy over me well of course they went crazy
with your running and jumping your boobies jiggled like crazy all over the place so the guys loved it
they saw your panties during the play too you're telling me they weren't mesmerized by my brilliant
performance they were excited about a panty shark that's so awesome sounds like a tragically hilarious
case of meat acting meat like to me wow you were so close yet oh so far i was not you shot your face
see this proves the school festival is no place for people with no lives so we should sit it out and let
them have their fun so kotaka i was wondering who do you think you're gonna spend the day of the
festival with i know the neighbors club can present our own special event in the culture portion of
the school festival no we can't what do you mean we can't it's perfect for us this kind of cheesy
stuff is pretty much our club's thing she's right if anything's our formula it's this and if you think
about it this will be great practice for when we go to festivals with friends it can be new research
good idea no no it's not no objections to it you guys hold on big brother's wish is my command
what's wrong now yozara nothing fine you're just really stupid very well the neighbors club will
participate in this year's school festival we shall take hold of those real lifers in the middle of their
festivities and we'll cast them into hell where they belong understood completely yep i'm in let's go
i don't know casting them into hell seems a little extreme all right first we have to decide what we
want to contribute as a group how about a maid cafe go die what's wrong with that everyone knows a maid
cafe is the easiest path to festival victory don't be such an idiot meat isn't it obvious i'm not the
kind of girl who can wait on customers yeah i can't imagine yozara ever being able to manage that
especially not dressed up as a maid i just pictured yozara wearing a maid outfit waiting on customers
and it was the funniest thing i've ever imagined all my sides sure it's true that i'm not very good at
customer service so what i mean it's not like any of you are either hey give me a break i think i can at
least handle that much though i have no experience yeah right if kodaka tried customer service all the
customers would run away don't be rude they would not i can act nice whenever i want to but the
problem is you never want to okay miss know-it-all then what about you can you do customer service
you should know by now not to underestimate the power of genius inventor rika shigama hey yozara
do you have the maid costume yukumura wore when we thought he was a boy yeah i think so hold on
rika might as well try the outfit on so she can practice it right close your eyes rika is going to
change clothes so no peeking got it you may open your eyes now
your face is telling rika you've simply acknowledged rika is wearing maid clothes
however you don't have any comments in particular on the matter you're right about that that was
pretty cool you just totally read my mind you're an imbecile why are you so stupid kodaka and you
kept your eyes closed the whole time i was changing you moron you were supposed to sneak a peek
what for what for forget about it listen up jack wagon get your boneheaded ass out of this room and
come back in again you know you've had a really foul mouth lately
you twisted twat face with pudding for brains oh geez rika what the hell was that for shut up and sit
down in your chair you clown bitch i said sit down you understand you're being kicked but for some
reason you can't grasp the idea of sitting your ass down what kind of poorly trained fleabag are you
rika seriously questions whether there are brains in that thick skull of yours which by the way is
the color of her poop after she eats curry stop you can't do whatever you want just because you've
randomly decided to be a dominatrix rika says huh good grief rika doesn't remember giving a brainless
dog permission to sit in the chair of a human being fine then just tell me where you want me to sit
there's a chair right in front of you unfortunately it's invisible to fools
rika is going to set this here but it is not for you and just so you know the coffee costs 980 yen
is that understood i can't believe you're gonna charge me for coffee i didn't even order and it's
expensive whatever just take off your pants and pathetically humiliate yourself in public by exposing
your privates as you enjoy the diabolical combination of coffee aroma and the stench of your own crotch
you perverted worm please i'm begging you i can't take anymore promise that you'll come back to see
rika again not on your life come on admit it you love seeing rika like this how can i admit to liking
something that was so brutal to me well that's unexpected rika was sure this attitude would be
quite popular illogical thought process aside this could be a good direction for us to take no i beg to
differ on that what did you think yukimura i'm afraid your skills are still somewhat immature oh well
you're a former maid right so do you think you could teach us the essence of what a real maid should be
yes the essence of a maid simple it is complete and utter devotion to big brother okay you're up
next care to give us a little taste of your customer service skill set uh you want to see me rika knows
she does come on senna rika bets you're really good at it guess i don't have a choice
all righty kotika i'm gonna change now so go wait in the hallway i can't just close my eyes like i did
before no of course not i mean we already have two full strikes on our records so our what never mind
just get out of here what's her problem
you can come in now kotika welcome home master how has your day been oh uh is that too small
stop staring at me like that god how did you two fit into this it's like crazy tight i can barely
even break holy you can say that again okay holy what would you like we have special made sandwiches
special made tea and coffee special made yummy cake we have whatever your little heart desires so what
will it be master coffee i guess that sounds great coffee it is coming right up master
i'm really confused right now how come you're so good at doing this it's not all that confusing
uh i'm just uh oh i'm just copying stella that's all is that what it is you have a professional
butler at home so that's almost the same thing totally almost exactly so you have a professional
butler i fail to see how watching a butler would make you the perfect cafe mate well whatever it is
you're really good stop flattering me silly wait i forgot i have to do a spell to make it taste better
what kind of spell taste better taste better now okay yummy um that kind really uh yes miss master really
really really really really really really really meat
no i don't visit maid cafes as much as i can when i'm not at school leave me alone
all right made cafes are off the table
see ya i'm heading home now cool
all right hey yo zara i forgot i had something to ask
uh no wait it's it's not i uh this isn't what it looks like kotaka i swear to you uh i have reason
i mean wait no
leos this week be sure and keep your eyes out for a disturbance in the force because if you don't have
the right attitude about it you might end up hurting your friends like i have any friends
anyway what are you doing today do you have any more makeup classes i do not today marks the end of
my two-week-long ordeal i am free to live as i please must be a relief huh maybe next time try not to fail
your classes
hmm let's see i like the idea of a fortune telling booth please tell me you don't really believe in
that stuff well not personally no but i guess i thought a lot of people liked having their fortunes
told especially high school girls not me i don't buy any of that bs i mean when you're chosen by god
every day is your lucky day i don't need some wrinkled old hag to tell me how wonderful my life is
you're exactly right mate huh you are blessed and every day is your lucky day
yo zara so you admit the truth i do you've been lucky every single day of your life meaning you've
hit your luck ceiling there's nowhere else to go you will never make a new friend the girls at school
will forever hate and shun you so they'll keep ganging up on you which means you'll always be alone in gym
class when people pair up for home ec or a field trip someone will inevitably say hey cena why don't you
pair up with a boy and then everyone will laugh your memories will be ruined and right now is the
happiest your life will ever be rude much how can you say that for what it's worth rika thinks you
should just try to be happy anyway i feel so sad now poor poor cena you don't really believe her do
you still though i think i can get behind the fortune telling idea are you a believer in that kind of
thing yo zara no i absolutely am not for three months in middle school i checked every fortune i
could get my hands on tv newspapers magazines i checked them all i also recorded in detail everything
that happened to me on those days afterwards i objectively assessed my so-called luck tallied
it against all the fortunes and collected the statistics not a single fortune had an accuracy
rate higher than seven percent therefore i decided i could not believe in fortune telling by taking it
to that extreme you seem more than a little fortune obsessed for real more importantly why are you
agreeing to do the booth after all that all we have to do is make up a bunch of random crap then we'll be
able to screw over all the real life havers who are unintelligent enough to take fortune telling
seriously i can't imagine anything more fun than that how cruel you're an actual witch aren't you if you
ask me i think you sound crazy meat i'll read your fortune as an experiment why would you want to do that
yes i see it uh see what something is troubling thee right now is it not troubling me for real thee it is
something to do with thy relationships well now that you mention it yeah i guess that's accurate i know
thou art giving off a faint purple mist a mist that symbolizes uneasiness i can tell from the shape
of the mist that relationships are the root of this trouble in your life right now wow you're right
a hundred percent yes because i see it and know with all things i can also tell thou generally thinkest
in a manner which brings about a positive attitude however occasionally thou feelest regret how could you
know all that and here we go thou hast certain gifts gifts that are far and above what those you
find around you have been given yet i can sense thou are often frustrated at not being able to express
these gifts to their fullest though thou hast an optimistic side at times thou waverest about
thy actions and decisions growing worrisome and whilst thou art normally cheerful thou art also prone to
great loneliness impossible tell me how you know that hey this type of reaction has a name doesn't it
yeah that's right it's called the barnum effect it's a psychological phenomenon where in the subject
when told general things that could apply to anyone takes them to be an accurate personal diagnosis
you know i honestly didn't expect you to understand me so well yosura how funny it's making me feel
happier in a way and she fell for a hook line and sinker shocking i am willing to tell thee a way
to immediately improve the life of a sweet yet awkward person such as thyself if thou art willing
to listen really tell me i'm listening tonight at midnight on the dot thou must go to the roof and
balance a bowl of water upon thy head turning around three times whilst giving an eerie shriek and
shouting sexy beam loud enough for the whole house to hear if the water doth not spill from the bowl
thou shalt attain the moon's blessing and thy life will be visited by great fortune shut the hell up oh
thank you yosura i've misjudged you and i'm so sorry it's not a problem go forth now may thee be happy
you get me
senna daddy spanked me so hard but i don't mind if it's for my happiness
oh crap don't tell me she actually did it
i don't know what do you want me you skank how dare you trick me like that trick you why whatever
do you mean that fortune telling yesterday you made up that stupid mean lie it was so mean and hateful
and then hey don't let your dad get you so upset his favorite pastime is yelling at you about the
stupid stuff you always do it's kind of his thing that's not the issue yesterday i felt so happy i had hope
again you i don't know you just really you just you're so mean and dumb you're mean and dumb
i feel like crap so i hope you're happy
come on let's go ahead and go to the club room okay
i have been awaiting your arrival my other half oh hi
hey you're here it feels like it's been forever right what up girl did you just come by
to hang out with me too cute oh you are my angel
what the hell are you looking at oh nothing never mind
how lucky am i that i get to see you today am i right it seems that good fortune has visited you
after all all right i think i'm like totally back on a roll again what on earth could be luckier
than being visited by kobito look she's just here because she doesn't have to stay after school to
make up classes anymore yes i suppose that is right this has nothing whatsoever to do with yozara's
mean old fake magic so you say but how will you ever know for sure you know that right there is why
nobody likes you well it's whatever i'll forgive you this time there's no sense being mad when kobito's
here huh like i care what spoiled meat thinks about me
glad you're finally back with us
so have we decided whether or not we're doing the fortune telling booth for the festival yet
rika brought reference books with her just in case cool i don't know rika i guess we can decide later
agreed
birthday fortune telling oh hey that reminds me guys kobito's got a birthday next week
seriously kobito's birthday that's what i said it's october 18th every year we have to celebrate
obviously
oh
At last, I have returned victorious from my long and brutal battle to the death.
Yeah, congratulations.
Now study every day so you don't fall behind and have to make the next test up.
I only failed that last exam because the Akashic Records randomly malfunctioned on me.
No more excuses, young lady. Get to studying.
Yeah, okay.
Next time, he's my brother, but as long as there's love, it doesn't matter if he gets more sisters, right?
Wait! Yes, it does matter!
Thank you.